Amanda Seals. Folks, dropped into our DMs at Seals said it on Instagram to share their secrets.
My granddaddy was like a pillar in our community. Everybody looked up to him. One day I'm rummaging
through some old family documents and I stumble upon some papers tucked away in my grandma's
attic. Ooh, the grandma attic is always a site for possible revelation. Turns out back in the day,
he was into embezzlement, fraud, you named it. He passed on now and I would never air him out
publicly, but damn, I'm the only one in the family that knows. Is that a secret you feel like you
could keep from your family, especially now that he's passed on or would you tell? Absolutely.
That's what we do in the Black family. We hold on to stuff and it'll be going generations and
generations and that one kid figures it out. But I had a friend, her grandmother was mean all the time
and then one day I was over the house and she just came over to me and started telling me about the
grandfather had a kid with somebody else. And I went back to the girl and I was like, yeah, you know,
your grandmother just told me the story and she knew nothing about it. And it caused this whole
thing in the family. And it was like, people was mad at me. And I was like, I don't know why she told
me that. Like, she just came out and said to me and told me the story. She was mad at him, I guess,
and was sort of like, do you believe? And, and, and she was shocked. And then it just caused,
like, I was never invited over the house again. The life and times of Colby Cole.